<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncertainty...Minimized</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Uncertainty...Minimized</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistically Verifying Claims Made in Childrens Stories</title>
      <link>/post/statistically-verifying-claims-made-in-childrens-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</author>
      <guid>/post/statistically-verifying-claims-made-in-childrens-stories/</guid>
      <description>Bedtime has historically been a battle for our family. Kids have this impressive ability to fall asleep when you want them awake and vigorously stay awake when you want them to sleep. To combat the insanity, we read a few books every night before bed. There is a great series of books for young children called &amp;ldquo;The Magic Tree House&amp;rdquo;. The series follows two children (Jack and Annie) who transport to other times and places for some mystery or adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Many Boys is Too Many?</title>
      <link>/post/how-many-is-too-many/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</author>
      <guid>/post/how-many-is-too-many/</guid>
      <description>Anyone who has multiple boys in a row at some point asks themselves a question: did I just get ‘lucky’ or are we only able to have boys? As you can see, we certainly asked that question… When we had our third boy in a row I started to wonder: how many children do you have to have of a given sex before you can statistically conclude that there is something other than random chance influencing to the outcome?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Autoencoder Neural Networks for Maximal Christmas Decoration Enjoyment</title>
      <link>/post/deep-autoencoder-neural-networks-for-maximal-christmas-decoration-enjoyment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</author>
      <guid>/post/deep-autoencoder-neural-networks-for-maximal-christmas-decoration-enjoyment/</guid>
      <description>My wife loves decorations. From Valentines Day to Easter to Thanksgiving, our house is adorned with interesting festive items. Her favorite season by far is Christmas. Every December we drive around trying to find the best Christmas lights. Inevitably, there are a few houses with lights that blink with the music, something I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated with.
Two years ago I embarked on a mission to build my own Christmas Light Show, specifically this is what I had in mind:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</author>
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About mecode{white-space: pre;}pre:not([class]) {background-color: white;}if (window.hljs) {hljs.configure({languages: []});hljs.initHighlightingOnLoad();if (document.readyState &amp;&amp; document.readyState === &#34;complete&#34;) {window.setTimeout(function() { hljs.initHighlighting(); }, 0);}}h1 {font-size: 34px;}h1.title {font-size: 38px;}h2 {font-size: 30px;}h3 {font-size: 24px;}h4 {font-size: 18px;}h5 {font-size: 16px;}h6 {font-size: 12px;}.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</author>
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>I am the lead for a growing team of Data Scientists at Lockheed Martin. I have one of the coolest jobs in the world, allowing me to apply deep learning and machine learning algorithms to business problems in a broad variety of domains. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been focused on NLP, using CNN and LSTM based deep learning models to build end to end NLP pipelines.
I studied physics at The Colorado School of Mines and moved into the field of semiconductor reliability at IBM.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>