<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Uncertainty...Minimized</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Uncertainty...Minimized</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoder For Christmas 2: Tuning and Convolutions</title>
      <link>/post/autoencoder-for-christmas-2-tuning-and-convolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</author>
      <guid>/post/autoencoder-for-christmas-2-tuning-and-convolutions/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve found that while typically people are exposed to machine learning on clean datasets with with clear objectives, doing machine learning in real busness environments isn&amp;rsquo;t often that straightforward. You have to think more creatively about what you use for a training set and how you go about training your model. This is most prevelant in Natural Language Processing, where there isn&amp;rsquo;t typically clean labeled dataset for what you want (IMDB sentiment doesn&amp;rsquo;t work very well for the defense industry&amp;hellip;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Autoencoder Neural Networks for Maximal Christmas Decoration Enjoyment</title>
      <link>/post/deep-autoencoder-neural-networks-for-maximal-christmas-decoration-enjoyment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mj514316@domain.com (Michael C Johnson)</author>
      <guid>/post/deep-autoencoder-neural-networks-for-maximal-christmas-decoration-enjoyment/</guid>
      <description>My wife loves decorations. From Valentines Day to Easter to Thanksgiving, our house is adorned with interesting festive items. Her favorite season by far is Christmas. Every December we drive around trying to find the best Christmas lights. Inevitably, there are a few houses with lights that blink with the music, something I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated with.
Two years ago I embarked on a mission to build my own Christmas Light Show, specifically this is what I had in mind:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>